Every body has a secret.
The Autopsy of Jane Doe is a horror, mystery film directed by André Øvredal.
Father and son coroners receive a mysterious unidentified
corpse with no apparent cause of death.
As they attempt to examine the "Jane Doe," they discover increasingly
bizarre clues that hold the key to her terrifying secrets.
Austin Tilden, played by Emile Hirsch.
Tommy Tilden, played by Brian Cox.
Emma, played by Ophelia Lovibond.
Jane Doe, played by Olwen Catherine Kelly.
Sheriff Sheldon, played by Michael McElhatton.
Officer Cole, played by Parker Sawyers.
The Autopsy of Jane Doe is a 2016 supernatural horror film directed
by André Øvredal as his first English-language film.
It stars Brian Cox and Emile Hirsch as father-and-son coroners who experience supernatural
phenomena while examining the body of an unidentified woman (played by Olwen Kelly).
The film premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September
9, 2016, and IFC Midnight released it on December 21, 2016.
It grossed $6 million at the box office.
The critical consensus at Rotten Tomatoes calls it "a
smart, suggestively creepy thriller".
The film explores themes of parent child relationship,
supernatural, crematorium, autopsy, morgue.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.